harman.com 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Harman

### 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Who We Are:  **

This web site is operated by or on behalf of Harman International Industries, Incorporated ("referred to as "Harman", "we", "our" and "us"). Harman's registered address is:

Harman International Industries, Incorporated 

400 Atlantic Street, 15th Floor

Stamford, CT 06901, USA

+1.203.328.3500

**Introduction:**

Harman provides you this privacy policy to explain to you how Harman and its third-party vendors collects, uses and protects your personal information when you visit Harman’s web sites and when you use Harman’s products. Harman respects your privacy and is committed to securing your personal information. This privacy policy was last updated on March 31, 2016.  By using this website, you consent to our privacy policy and acknowledge that it is subject to our Terms of Use.

**Collecting and Using Your Personal Information:**

Harman and its third-party vendors collect the personal information that you provide to us, as well as information automatically collected when you interact with this website, through cookies and analytics tracking tools, which help us evaluate the performance of our website, advertise on sites across the internet, show customized ads based on past visits to our website, and provide you with a better user experience. 

Harman may use your personal information that you provide to us in the process of establishing an account on our website in the following ways:

  1. Obtain your name for purposes of communicating with you and identifying you as a user of the web site.
  2. Verify your age as older than 13.
  3. Verify your age as older than 18 or that you have obtained your parent’s or guardian’s permission to use the web site.
  4. Send you a catalogue.
  5. Send you communications upon your request or consent.
  6. Allow you to participate in a promotion or other web site feature.
  7. Customize and/or personalize your communications and shopping experience with Harman.
  8. Better respond to your customer concerns and complaints.
  9. Keep you informed of Harman’s upcoming product releases unless you otherwise opt out of such messages.

Harman may use your personal information that you provide to us in the process of making a purchase in the following ways:

  1. Confirm your use of a valid credit card (or other authorized methods of payment).
  2. Process your payment via a credit card (or other authorized methods of payment).
  3. Send you the products that you purchased.

To fulfill your product orders, we may also disclose your personal information to our affiliates, third party service providers or distributors. 

Harman and its third-party vendor s also gather non-descriptive, non-personal information about how many visitors use our website. Harman does not collect any personal information about you in this instance but Harman may collect information that a user has visited the website for statistical analysis of the public’s use of our website. 

**Unsubscribing, Removing or Modifying Your Information:**

Harman appreciates that you may change your mind about our use of your personal information in the future. Harman offers several ways you can inform us about your privacy preferences:

  1. All email messages and newsletters will provide a description on how you can ask us to stop sending you messages and newsletters.
  2. At any time, you can send us an email at the address provided below.
  3. At any time, you can call our customer service number and request that you would like to change your marketing preferences.
  4. To modify or delete entirely the information you have provided during registration, please login and update your profile.

Please note that if you have unsubscribed from our communications, you may still receive communications already in production until your request is fully processed. If you request that your registration information be deleted or if you unsubscribe from communications, we may maintain information about sales transactions or service inquiries for future service and record keeping purposes.

**Online Tracking:**

A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Harman or its third-party vendors may use cookies to improve your experience with our website and show you ads based on past visits to our website. Harman may use cookies to improve Harman’s understanding of your likes and dislikes about our website, what you like and do not like on our website, customize the website to your prior uses and to generally improve all customer needs and interests.  You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. You may also delete cookies from your computer or opt out of a third party’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices)

**DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURES**

The “Do Not Track” standard is still in development and not yet finalized.  We will only collect and use the personal information you provide to us pursuant to the terms in this privacy policy.

**DISCLOSURE AND SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

Harman does not rent, sell or disclose your personal information or contact information to third parties for the third party’s own purposes. Harman may share your information with Harman’s affiliates under the same control of Harman as permitted under this privacy policy. In the event Harman is reorganized or transferred to a third party, your personal information may be transferred to the successor of Harman for the purposes and subject to the terms of this privacy policy. Harman (or, for consumers outside the United States, our distributor) may provide your credit card (or other authorized payment method) information to Harman’s bank or credit card or other authorized payment processor solely for purposes of processing your payment. Harman may also share your information with delivery services or international distributors to ship products to you. On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

**PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION:**

Harman engages the use of numerous technological security measures to preserve the security of your information, including without limitation, encryption technologies and authentication tools. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have a need to access your personal information for purposes of managing our website and providing you information as you have requested. All orders are placed through a secure server. Please be aware that no electronic data transmission over the internet can be 100% secure. 

**TRANSFERRING YOUR INFORMATION OVERSEAS:**

If you are located outside of the United States, Harman may transfer your information to Harman’s affiliates under the same control as Harman, to other service providers or distributors outside of your country or territory. Harman manages its website from the United States. Harman acknowledges that the data protection laws and other laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those of your country or territory and Harman will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights are respected.  When transferring personal data outside of the European Union, we require all third parties that are not Harman affiliates to agree to the [EU Model Contracts](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/transfer/index_en.htm), or contracts with similar provisions and safeguards.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:**

We respect the privacy of children. Our website is not designed to attract an audience younger than 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. Please contact us using the contact details below if you believe we may have collected information from your child, and we will work to delete it. 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS:**

Under California laws, California residents can request information from Harman whether Harman has disclosed a person’s personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Harman will not sell or share your personal information with non-Harman companies for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. California residents desiring to request further information about our compliance with these laws or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies are welcome to contact us using the contact information below. 

**OBTAINING A COPY OF OR UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

You can contact Harman at any time to obtain the personal information Harman possesses about you, or modify any personal information Harman retains that is incorrect. Please let us know what information you would like to receive from us, or what information is incorrect, and we will respond to you. Your request should include your name and proof of your identity. 

**CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

We will notify you when we make any material changes or updates to this privacy policy, including any material changes in how we use or share your personal information.

**QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK:**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. 

**NOTICE AND CONTACT INFORMATION:**

For questions or concerns, please email us or contact us at: 

**VIA EMAILS:  **

Harman International Industries, Incorporated   
400 Atlantic Street, 15th Floor   
Stamford, CT 06901, USA   
+1.203.328.3500 

**TERMS OF USE:**

Please also visit our “Terms of Use” section that explains other terms governing the use of our websites.
